gclexperts.com 2014-11-22

# Immigration Expert Services

GCLexperts is committed to safeguarding your privacy while providing our Secure Green Card Lottery online application services. We encourage you to periodically review this statement as it may change from time to time at our sole discretion. This Privacy Policy statement explains the personal information gathering and use practices of GCLexperts Organization. Questions concerning your personal information should be directed to our Privacy Officer by e-mail at [privacy@GCLexperts.com](mailto:privacy@Usafis.org)

**Information Collected**

GCLexperts collects personal identifiable information about you (your “Data”) at the time of purchase such as:

• Name  
• Age  
• Gender  
• Address  
• Phone and/or mobile numbers  
• Country  
• Zip code  
• Email  
• IP address and browser information  
• Market research data such as customer usage patterns

**Use and Disclosure of Personal Information**

We use your Data for legitimate business operational and marketing purposes, which may include:

• Enhancing our customer service  
• Processing orders and inquiries  
• Improving our website and services  
• Resolving disputes, collecting fees, and troubleshooting problems.  
• Conducting market research surveys.  
• Occasionally offering current subscribers the chance to participate in contests.  
• Providing you with information about products and services we offer.  **You may stop the delivery** of marketing emails by following the instructions accompanying a particular communication or by contacting us at ** **[privacy@GCLexperts.com](mailto:privacy@Usafis.org)

GCLexperts Organization may share information about users with business partners, sponsors and other third parties. We provide this information in aggregate form so that no individual user is identified.  **If** you prefer not to receive online marketing information from third-party companies, please contact our Privacy Officer by e-mail at ** **[privacy@GCLexperts.com **.**](mailto:privacy@Usafis.org)

GCLexperts sends messages to its subscribers via email regarding its products, new services, improvements, notice of scheduled services, etc. Our subscribers may opt-out of receiving this information by suspending their subscription with us.

**Payment Collection Information**

When purchasing a product using a credit card, you will be asked to submit data such as the credit card number and details. GCLexperts is hosted on a secure server and uses the most updated information security technology, whose purpose is to protect your credit card details during the transmission of data stored on the servers. This SSL technology (‘Secure Sockets Layers’), secures billions of dollars’ worth of transactions over the internet. GCLexperts uses a mediator such as PayPal and GiroPay for the purpose of providing alternative payment solutions.

**Security Policy**

GCLexperts has appropriate measures in place to help ensure that our users’ Data is protected against unauthorized access or use, alteration, unlawful or accidental destruction and accidental loss. Although we make reasonable efforts to protect your Personal Information from loss, misuse, or alteration by third parties, you should be aware that there is always some risk involved in transmitting information over the Internet.

We have adopted security tools and procedures that limit access to private and personal information as well as locates and prevents access from unauthorized users. While our security measures exceed the industry standards and we have not received any complaints about the penetrability of our security system, there is some risk that thieves could find a way to thwart our security systems.

We utilize ‘Cookies’ on your computer in order to simplify the user’s experience. You can set your browser preferences to a ‘cookie’ rejecting mode, but be advised that the service may not function properly. GCLexperts data is stored behind ‘Firewalls’ so as to prevent loss, changing or misuse of information under our control.

GCLexperts includes links to different sites. Please note that when ‘clicking’ any of these links, your computer will be directed to another separate website. We advise that you read the Privacy Protection Notice on these sites, since theirs may differ from ours.

**Access to Data and Contact Info**

You may request a copy or send a correction of the personal information we hold about you by contacting the Privacy Officer at [privacy@GCLexperts.com](mailto:privacy@Usafis.org) or writing to:

Privacy Officer:

GCLexperts

366 Amsterdam Avenue # 163 

NEW YORK, NY 10024

**Changes to this Policy**

Periodically, we may make changes to this privacy policy statement or the manner of use of your personal information to reflect any changes to our privacy practices. We will notify you about material changes to this Privacy Policy by placing a prominent notice on our website.
